Finding Aid for Engineering Communications & Marketing (University of Michigan) records 1860-2010
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan 1998
- Faculty Background Files
  - Jamie Phillips (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Richard L. Phillips (AERO) (Box 31)
  - Leland E. Pierce (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Christophe Pierre (MEAM) (Box 31)
  - Stephen M. Pollock (IOE) (Box 31)
  - Tresa Pollock (MSE) (Box 31)
  - Donald J. Portman (AOSS) (Box 31)
  - Kenneth G. Powell (AERO) (Box 31)
  - John E. Powers (Chem.) (Box 31)
  - Sandeep Pradham (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Atul Prakash (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Peter P. Pronko (EECS) (Box 31)
  - Leland J. Quackenbush (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Dragomar Radev (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Stephen C. Rand (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Klaus M. Rathfelder (CEE) (Box 32)
  - Lawrence Rauch (AERO) (Box 32)
  - Gabriel M. Rebeiz (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Thomas B. Reed (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Steven Reinhardt (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Nilton Renno (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - William B. Ribbens (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Aaron Ridley (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Richard E. Robertson (MSE) (Box 32)
  - Philip L. Roe (AERO) (Box 32)
  - William L. Root (AERO, EECS) (Box 32)
  - William C. Rounds (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Christopher Ruf (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Wadi S. Rumman (CEE) (Box 32)
  - Romesh Saigal (IOE) (Box 32)
  - Kazuhiro Saitou (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Karem A. Sakallah (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Perry J. Samson (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Kamal Sarabandi (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Ann Marie Sastry (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Phillip E. Savage (Chem.) (Box 32)
  - Thomas M. Sawyer (Tech. Comm.) (Box 32)
  - Daniel J. Scheeres (AERO) (Box 32)
  - Albert B. Schultz (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - William W. Schultz (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Nathan A. Schwadron (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Johannes Schwank (Chem.) (Box 32)
  - Norman R. Scott (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Raymond C. Scott (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Richard A. Scott (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Leonard Segel (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Lawrence Seiford (IOE) (Box 32)
  - Jeremy D. Semrau (CEE) (Box 32)
  - Thomas B. A. Senior (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Edward M. Shafter Jr. (Humanities) (Box 32)
  - Dushyant Sharma (IOE) (Box 32)
  - William E. Sharp (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Charles B. Sharpe (EECS) (Box 32)
  - John A. Shaw (AERO) (Box 32)
  - Pauline M. Sherman (AERO) (Box 32)
  - Jianjun Shi (IOE, MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Yaoyun Shi (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Kang G. Shin (IOE) (Box 32)
  - Tong W. Shyn (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Martin Sichel (AERO) (Box 32)
  - Volker Sick (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Sanford Sillman (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Jasprit Singh (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Maurice J. Sinnott (Chem.) (Box 32)
  - Ana Sirviente (NAME) (Box 32)
  - Wilbert R. Skinner (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Steven Skerlos (MEAM) (Box 32)
  - Henryk Skolimowski (Humanities) (Box 32)
  - Robert L. Smith (IOE) (Box 32)
  - Michael J. Solomon (Chem.) (Box 32)
  - Elliot Soloway (EECS) (Box 32)
  - Lee H. Somers (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Paul Song (AOSS) (Box 32)
  - Richard E. Sonntag (MEAM) (Box 33)
  - Peter J. Sousounis (AOSS) (Box 33)
  - Greg Spooner (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Keeran R. Srinivasan (Chem.) (Box 33)
  - Stephen S. Stanton (Humanities) (Box 33)
  - Wayne Stark (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Duncan G. Steel (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Anna Stefanopoulou (MEAM) (Box 33)
  - Jeffrey L. Stein (MEAM) (Box 33)
  - Nicholas Steneck (IOE) (Box 33)
  - Dwight W. Stevenson (Tech. Comm.) (Box 33)
  - Quentin F. Stout (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Martin J. Strauss (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Victor L. Streeter (CEE) (Box 33)
  - Jamin Sugih (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Robert Sulewski (Tech. Comm.) (Box 33)
  - Jianping (J. P.) Sun (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Jing Sun (NAME) (Box 33)
  - Dennis Sylvester (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Maria M. Szerszen (CEE) (Box 33)
  - Chen-to Tai (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Shuichi Takayama (BiomedE) (Box 33)
  - John E. Taylor (AERO), MEAM) (Box 33)
  - Daniel Teichroew (IOE) (Box 33)
  - M. Rasin Tek (Chem.) (Box 33)
  - Demosthenis Teneketzis (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Toby J. Teorey (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Fred L. Terry, Jr. (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Richmond H. Thomason (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Levi T. Thompson, Jr. (Chem.) (Box 33)
  - Michael Thouless (MEAM) (Box 33)
  - Tseng-Ying Tien (MSE) (Box 33)
  - Dawn M. Tilbury (MEAM) (Box 33)
  - Egons Tons (CEE) (Box 33)
  - Nicolas Triantafyllidis (AERO) (Box 33)
  - Armin W. Troesch (NAME) (Box 33)
  - Gary S. Tyson (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Fawwaz T. Ulaby (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Sheryl Ulin (IOE) (Box 33)
  - A. Galip Ulsoy (MEAM) (Box 33)
  - Donald P. Umstadter (EECS, NERS) (Box 33)
  - Steven Underwood (EECS, IOE) (Box 33)
  - Juris Upatnieks (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Deborah Van Hoewyk (Tech. Comm.) (Box 33)
  - Bram van Leer (AERO) (Box 33)
  - Dietrich H. Vincent (NERS) (Box 33)
  - Nguyen X. Vinh (AERO) (Box 33)
  - Nickolas Vlahopoulos (NAME) (Box 33)
  - John L. Volakis (EECS) (Box 33)
  - Anthony Waas (AERO) (Box 33)
  - Harue Wada (MSE) (Box 33)
  - J. Hunter Waite Jr. (AOSS) (Box 33)
  - Gregory H. Wakefield (EECS) (Box 33)
  - David T. Walker (NAME) (Box 33)
  - James C. G. Walker (AOSS) (Box 33)
  - Richard Wallace (Tech. Comm.) (Box 34)
  - Henry Y. Wang (Chem.) (Box 34)
  - Fred C. Ward, Jr. (Tech. Comm.) (Box 34)
  - Gary S. Was (MSE, NERS) (Box 34)
  - Peter D. Washabaugh (AERO) (Box 34)
  - Kimberly M. Wasserman (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Walter J. Weber, Jr. (CEE) (Box 34)
  - David K. Wehe (NERS) (Box 34)
  - Michael Wellman (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Terry E. Weymouth (EECS) (Box 34)
  - John F. Whitaker (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Chelsea C. White III (IOE) (Box 34)
  - James K. Wight (CEE) (Box 34)
  - James O. Wilkes (Chem.) (Box 34)
  - G. Brymer Williams (Chem.) (Box 34)
  - William J. Williams (EECS) (Box 34)
  - William W. Willmarth (AERO) (Box 34)
  - Richard C. Wilson (IOE) (Box 34)
  - Alan Stuart Wineman (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - Herbert G. Winful (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Kim Allen Winick (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Kensall D. Wise (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Richard D. Woods (CEE) (Box 34)
  - John B. Woodward (NAME) (Box 34)
  - Margaret S. Wooldridge (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - Charles B. Woolley (IOE) (Box 34)
  - Steven J. Wright (CEE) (Box 34)
  - C. F. Jeff Wu (IOE) (Box 34)
  - Qian Wu (AOSS) (Box 34)
  - E. Benjamin Wylie (CEE) (Box 34)
  - Andrew E. Yagle (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Raymond A. Yagle (NAME) (Box 34)
  - Steven M. Yalisove (MSE) (Box 34)
  - Lumin Wang (NERS) (Box 34)
  - Ralph T. Yang (Chem.) (Box 34)
  - Wei-Hsuin Yang (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - Wen-Jei Yang (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - Victor Yanovsky (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Albert F. Yee (MSE) (Box 34)
  - Gregory S. Y. Yeh (Chem.) (Box 34)
  - Derek Yip-Hoi (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - David Young (AOSS) (Box 34)
  - Edwin H. Young (Chem.), MSE) (Box 34)
  - John G. Young (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - Jingxia Yuan (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - Hongyan Zhang (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - Rachel Zhang (IOE) (Box 34)
  - Zhi-Fang Zhang (MEAM) (Box 34)
  - Robert M. Ziff (Chem.) (Box 34)
  - George J. Zissis (EECS) (Box 34)
  - Thomas H. Zurbuchen (AOSS) (Box 34)
Related Material
Researchers seeking additional information on the College of Engineering are advised to consult the following related record groups at the Bentley Historical Library: University of Michigan College of Engineering, and Camp Davis (University of Michigan